desiringgod.org 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Desiring God

We greatly value the trust you place in us. The personal information we collect on our website is strictly limited to the information you provide to us when you (i) make an online contribution, (ii) create an online account, (iii) sign up for one of our mailing lists, or (iv) contact us (e.g., send us an email or call us at a number listed on the site). This information will not be given to or shared with anyone outside of Desiring God or our service providers unless you expressly allow it, or we believe that it is necessary to comply with the law, protect a person’s safety, or address fraud or security issues.

### Online Contributions

When you make a donation on our website, the personal information you provide to us is used to process your donation and add you to our donor email list. This information is protected using SSL encryption. Your payment information is securely transmitted to our payment processor in order to process the contribution and it is not stored on our end. We maintain your name, email address, and donation amount in order to comply with accounting requirements, manage receipting and provide your donation history.

### Online Accounts

When you create an online account with us, we collect your email address and other contact information you provide when creating your account. You can access and update this information at any time, as well as your mailing list subscription information and preferences, and view your online donation history by [logging in](https://www.desiringgod.org/users/log-in) to your account.

### Mailing Lists

When you sign up for one of our mailing lists, we collect your name and email address. We use this information to send you what you’ve requested from us (e.g., the latest “Ask Pastor John” article). We do not sell, license, or share our mailing lists (email or physical), or your name and email address, with anyone outside of our organization. If you want to change, update or remove your name and email address on our list, you can do that by [logging in](https://www.desiringgod.org/users/log-in) to your account or contacting us at email@desiringGod.org.

### Usage Tracking

We track the way people use our website, apps, and email to provide you with a better and more engaging experience. Our servers automatically record user information such as Internet Protocol (IP) address, device and browser type, operating system, pages or features browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, frequency of use, terms searched, hyperlinks clicked on or used, and other use-related statistics. We use this information to provide the features of our website and apps, and to analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance our users’ experience, by expanding the features and functionality we provide and tailoring it to our users’ needs and preferences. We may also use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends and track users’ movements around our website. You can control use of cookies on most web browsers.

### Amazon.com Disclosure

Desiring God is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

### Children’s Online Privacy

We never knowingly collect or maintain information on our website from visitors we know are under the age of 13.

### Accessing and Managing Your Private Information

You can view and manage your online account profile, mailing list subscriptions, and recurring donations by [logging in](https://www.desiringgod.org/users/log-in) to your online account here. You can also make a change, get a copy, or delete all of the private information we have associated with you by emailing us at email@desiringGod.org.

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version will always be posted here. By continuing to use our website and apps, and by communicating with us via this site and email, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.
